Hey, boy
Who even are you
My mind is a complete mess
It's like I'm literally glitching
Mayday
Because of you
I'm losing my mind
I think I'm falling in love with you
What do I do
I must be going crazy
Every single second, you're all I think about
I keep catching myself
Smiling for no reason
This is so not me
Tell me now
You want this too
Stop holding back
Just shoot your shot
Before the night fades away
One more chance
Set my heart on fire
I don't wanna let you go
Whisper in my ear, day after day
Tell me you miss me
Woo woo woo
Woo woo woo woo woo woo
It's a kind of love
Got me thunderstruck
I can't get enough of you ooh ah
Boy, you're really like one in a milli
Never gon let it fizzle out
You got me all in my feelings
Our love is the realest
And that's how we ride
Never alone, never wondering
Cause you forever my future
Tell me now
You want this too
Stop holding back
Just shoot your shot
Before the night fades away
One more chance
Set my heart on fire
I don't wanna let you go
Whisper in my ear, day after day
Tell me you miss me
Woo woo woo
Woo woo woo woo woo woo
How you feel like that
I like it, I like it